<!DOCTYPE resources [<!ENTITY appname "Application Template"><!ENTITY companyname "MyCompany"><!ENTITY priv_pol_date "2022-11-04"><!ENTITY email "minemodsdownload@gmail.com">]>

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">&appname;</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>

    <string name="share_text">"A good template for an Android application"</string>

    <string name="app_descr">"This project is a template for single-page applications for any subject area.\n
        <b>Where to use:</b>\n
        &#8226; Commercial.\n
        &#8226; Educational.\n
        &#8226; Any.\n
        "</string>
    <string name="priv_policy">Privacy Policy</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_text">
        "<b>Privacy Policy</b>\n\n &companyname; has created the &appname; app as a free app. This service is provided by &companyname;
        free of charge and to use any user interface.
This page is used to inform users of our policy for the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decides to use our application.
If you choose to use our app, you agree to the collection and use of this policy. The personal information we collect is used to provide and improve the app. We will not use your information to anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as in our Terms and Conditions, which are available in Minecraft mods, if defined in this Privacy Policy.\n
        <b>Collection and use of information</b>\n
        To use our application, we may require you to provide us with certain personal information. The information we provide will be stored by us and the internet as described in this privacy policy.
The app uses third party services that may collect information used to identify you.
Link to the privacy policy of third party service providers applied by the application\n
        &#8226; <a href="https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/">Google Play Services</a>\n
        &#8226; <a href="https://support.google.com/admob/answer/6128543?hl=en">AdMob</a>\n
        &#8226; <a href="https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics">Google Analytics for Firebase</a>\n
        &#8226; <a href="https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/">Firebase Crashlytics</a>\n
        &#8226; <a href="https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update/printable">Facebook</a>\n
        <b>Data</b>\n
        We want to inform you that whenever you use our application, in the event of an error in the application, we collect data and information (through third parties) on your phone. This log data may include information such as your device\'s IP address, device name, operating system version of the Service you are using, the time and date you used the Service, and other statistics.\n
        <b>Cookies</b>\n
        Cookies are small data files that are commonly used as anonymous unique indicators. They are sent to your browser from the websites you visit and are stored in your device\'s internal memory.
This Service does not explicitly use these "cookies". However, the app may use third-party code and libraries that use cookies to collect information and improve its services. You have the option to accept these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. You choose to use some cookies.\n
        <b>Service providers</b>\n
        We may hire third party companies and individuals for the following reasons:\n
        &#8226; To facilitate the operation of our Service;\n
        &#8226; To provide the Service on our behalf;\n
        &#8226; To provide services related to the Service; or\n
        &#8226; To help us analyze how our Service is used.\n
        We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to carry out their assigned tasks on our behalf. However, they are required not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.\n
        <b>Security</b>\n
        We value your trust in providing us with your personal information, so we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect it. But remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure or reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n
        <b>Links to other sites</b>\n
        Our application may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third party link, you will be redirected to that site. Please note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we recommend that you familiarize yourself with the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over the content, policies, or actions of any third party sites or services.\n
        <b>Children\'s privacy</b>\n
        Our app is not intended for people under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from under the age of 13. We removed it from our servers. Let us know that you have provided us with the required action.\n
        <b>Changes to this Privacy Policy</b>\n
        We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Therefore, you are encouraged to periodically review this page for changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting a new Privacy Policy on this page.
This policy is effective from &priv_pol_date;\n
        <b>Contact us</b>\n
        If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at <a href="mailto:&email;">&email;</a>.
"
    </string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>


</resources>